jambase.com 2016-04-19

# Privacy Policy - JamBase

### Consumer Information

During the process of delivering our website (www.jambase.com), JamBase does not collect any personally identifiable information about you such as name, address, phone number, or e-mail address. However, JamBase may obtain some types of non-personally identifiable information such as the your browser type or the type of computer operating system you use (Macintosh or Windows, for example). The information collected by JamBase is used for the purpose of targeting ads and measuring ad effectiveness on behalf of our advertisers.

In some cases on JamBase and our subsidiary pages and sites (JamBase Festivals, JamBase Tickets, MyJamBase), you may voluntarily provide personal information either during registration or in response to a promotion that JamBase runs (a promotion may ask you to fill out a survey or provide your address or zip code for mailing prizes). If this does occur, JamBase may collect this information. JamBase may combine this information with other users' information and review it in an aggregate form to understand the type of individuals who view a specific type of ad or visit a particular kind of website. From time to time JamBase will run its own surveys in order to better understand its audience demographic. This information may be shared in aggregate form with advertisers, never individually.

### Cookies

Cookies are not required in order to access JamBase, but JamBase does use cookies to help make your JamBase experience more personalized and helpful to your individual needs. JamBase may set a cookie on your machine when you visit www.jambase.com. Cookies are mainly used to recognize users and grant access to the My JamBase area of www.jambase.com. Cookies are also used to remember users who select this "remember me" option when logging in to My JamBase.

### Security

We take all reasonable steps to protect personal information and we use technology such as encryption, access control procedures, firewalls and physical security. By using this Web site or registering for any JamBase service, you agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. Without limitation of the foregoing, you understand and agree that (1) the information collected by JamBase may be stored indefinitely, (2) JamBase may store, access and use the information in any jurisdiction, including jurisdictions in which the privacy laws may be different and less protective than those in your home jurisdiction and (3) JamBase may collect, process, use and disclose the information for a variety of purposes, including, without limitation, direct marketing by JamBase, advertisers and limited third parties to which JamBase may disclose the information.

### Registration, Login and Authentication

By registering or authenticating, Users allow this Application to identify them and give them access to dedicated services.

#### Facebook Authentication (Facebook, Inc.)

Facebook Authentication is a registration and authentication service provided by Facebook, Inc. and is connected to the Facebook social network. Personal Data collected: various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service. Place of processing: US - [Facebook Authentication Information](https://www.facebook.com/help/405977429438260)

### Advertising

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: [How to opt out](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)

### Legal Compliance

Notwithstanding anything else stated in this Privacy Policy, JamBase reserves the right to disclose your information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is reasonably necessary to (1) comply with legal process, (2) respond to any claims against it, or (3) protect the rights, property or personal safety of JamBase, our customers or the public. Otherwise, we have total respect for your privacy.

### Questions, Comments, Concerns

If you have any questions or comments about our use of personal information, please contact us using our [Web Contact Form](http://www.jambase.com/About/Contact/). We will use reasonable efforts to promptly investigate any complaint you may have regarding our use of personal information.

The short story: JamBase exists to help you **_Go See Live Music!_** , not to snoop into your private life.
